http://www.zymoresearch.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Zymo Research Corp. (“Zymo”)
Last Updated and Effective as of May 25, 2018
Zymo thanks you for using our products, values your privacy, and believes in treating others as we want to be treated.
Zymo’s privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) gives you information on how we collect, use, and sometimes transfer personal information when you visit our website (www.zymoresaerch.com) and other websites that we control (www.Epibeat.com) that include a direct link to this Privacy Policy (each a “website” or collectively “websites”). We ask that you review this policy thoroughly and contact us if there are any questions. Additionally, we are committed to making our data privacy practices transparent and have made updates to our Privacy Policy in accordance with and seek to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) requirements to the best of our knowledge.
Consent and Opting Out
By visiting our websites, ordering from us, or registering with us you accept and consent to this Privacy Policy. Thus, by providing your Personal information (“information” or “personal information”), you agree that we may collect, use, share and transfer that information in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
You may revoke this consent by contacting Zymo and revoking your consent at any time, requesting your information be deleted.
Contact Zymo
If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about this Privacy Policy or privacy-related practices, please contact Zymo by email at info@zymoresearch.com or phone at 949-679-1190.
Children
We do not to the best of our knowledge collect or use information from children under the age of 18.
Scope of Information Collected and Stored
Zymo’s privacy policy is simple: we collect no information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide information to us when you use our websites, order from us, or register with us or provide information to our personnel at trade shows. Zymo’s web servers or other computers and customer service personnel collect your contact information when you place orders. This includes name (personal or entity), address, phone number, facsimile number (Fax), email address, credit card number, or other identifier for billing or shipping in order for us to process and complete an order for our products or services. Also, sometimes we may ask you to voluntarily provide us or we may provide information to you about promotions, scientific interests, new products, technical updates or changes, contact preferences, and other information.
Tracking Technology
Zymo’s websites automatically uses cookies or other similar tracking tools or technology to track use and to facilitate and enhance the user experience (collectively “Cookies”). Cookies are small pieces of text that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. Our websites may use both Cookies that we implement and Cookies implemented by our suppliers and other third parties. With cookies in place, our system will recognize you whenever you use your web browser to connect to our page. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over Cookie to disable them but this may affect or stop you from using certain features of our websites such as interactive options or some purchasing features. You may choose not to take advantage of these interactive features and you can set your browser to reject Cookies or to alert you when a cookie has been sent. Due to this automatic collection of Cookies, we do not honor “do not track” requests. We do not have access or control over of third-party Cookies and consider them to be outside the scope of this Privacy Policy.
Uses Made of Information
Zymo uses your information for your benefit to make sure we can meet your needs when you order from us which we refer to our operations. We consider our operations as crucial to understanding your and fulfilling your orders for products and services, information requests (marketing collateral or technical information), meeting our other obligations, provide requested services and information, and update you on products, services and benefits, which may include marketing materials. If you order products or services through our websites, we may contact you by email to provide information about your order (e.g., confirmations, shipment notifications, guidelines for how best to use the product, etc.). If you have registered an account with us, we may also send you email regarding your account status or changes to relevant agreements or policies.
Aggregation
We may aggregate and combine information or use it to improve our websites operation. We also store information in compliance with GDPR requirements.
Storage, Security and Retention of Information
We use robust internal and third party physical and technical measures intended to safeguard your information and help protect this information from unauthorized access or loss. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any required passwords to access our websites (if any). We use our best efforts and comply with US state and federal and other law such as the GDPR (when applicable; EEA) for data security but cannot guarantee complete security. If you believe your data is compromised contact us and we will conduct a review and take action to rectify or mitigate any such compromise of your information.
We retain data for a reasonable time and at least as long as required by applicable law, and for periods of time needed for Zymo to pursue our obligation to meet your needs and other business needs (audits, quality management system compliance), legal obligations, dispute resolution or enforcing agreements. You may access, correct, and update your information by accessing your accounts or profiles, where relevant, on the websites or by contacting us via phone. You may request a summary of information we hold about you, as well as corrections, updates or deletion of your information, by contacting us at info@zymoresearch.com. Our response to such requests will be limited to information under our direct control. We will make best efforts to respond promptly to such requests in accordance with our legal obligations by applicable rules and laws.
Protection
We use information in connection with various legal proceedings from time to time to protect your or our rights. In this regard, In addition, we may disclose information about you to a third party at your request, or if you consent to the disclosure.
Transfer
We may share and transfer your information to our associated companies, affiliates, agents, vendors or service providers who assist us in the process of providing products and services to you or assist us in other ways. We do not sell or otherwise benefit monetarily from transferring your information. We also may disclose Information to third parties where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law, to cooperate with authorities (law enforcement) or to comply with a legal proceedings (public or private) or to protect the safety, rights, or property of you or us or the public. At some future date we may buy or sell or otherwise transfer a business unit or asset from or to another entity, we may share or transfer your information pursuant to the terms and conditions of any such transaction.
European Economic Area (EEA)
Legal Basis for Processing Your Personal information (EEA Only)
If you are located in the European Union or Switzerland and you have a data privacy or data use concern that you feel has not been fully addressed, you have the right to contact the relevant EU data protection authority or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and information Commissioner, as applicable.
If you are an individual from the EEA, our legal basis for collecting and using Personal information will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.
In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and will advise you whether or not the provision of your Personal information is mandatory, as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your Personal information. Similarly, if we collect and use your Personal information in reliance on our or a third party’s legitimate interests that are not already described in this Privacy Policy, we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are. If you have any questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us as indicated above.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy any time and at our sole discretion. Changes will be effective upon the date the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the websites, with the effective date noted in the Policy header at the top of this page. When you visit our websites, you accept the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at that time. We recommend that you periodically revisit and review this page to obtain the latest information on our privacy practices.
